Guide to the Dwight Hall, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, circa 1911-1980; Accession 1988-A-105
  - Page, Kirby, 1927-1944 (Box 40, Folder 1338)
  - Page, T. L., 1933 (Box 40, Folder 1339)
  - Pai - Pain, 1915-1935 (Box 40, Folder 1340)
  - Painter, Thomas, 1927-1936 (Box 40, Folder 1341)
  - Palmer, Arthur E., 1931-1946 (Box 40, Folder 1342)
  - Palmer, Howard S., 1940 (Box 40, Folder 1343)
  - Palmer, Hoyt, 1927-1946 (Box 40, Folder 1344)
  - Palmer, J. - Palmer W., 1921-1933 (Box 40, Folder 1345)
  - Pan - Pao, 1939-1940 (Box 40, Folder 1346)
  - Paradise, N. Burton, 1917-1936 (Box 40, Folder 1347)
  - Parcells, Charles A., 1919-1940 (Box 40, Folder 1348)
  - Pardee, William D., 1930-1938 (Box 40, Folder 1349)
  - Paret, Robert R., 1916 (Box 40, Folder 1350)
  - Paris, Irving, 1914 (Box 40, Folder 1351)
  - Park, Charles E., 1937-1941 (Box 40, Folder 1352)
  - Park, William Edgar, 1943 (Box 40, Folder 1353)
  - Parker, A. - Parker, E., 1926-1931 (Box 40, Folder 1354)
  - Parker, Eugenia, 1938-1940 (Box 40, Folder 1355)
  - Parker, F. - Parkh, 1928-1944 (Box 40, Folder 1356)
  - Parks, Elton, 1916-1939 (Box 40, Folder 1357)
  - Parn - Pars, 1915-1938 (Box 40, Folder 1358)
  - Parsons, Artley B., 1916-1940 (Box 40, Folder 1359)
  - Parsons, D. - Part, 1927-1944 (Box 40, Folder 1360)
  - Patch - Paton, 1919-1972 (Box 40, Folder 1361)
  - Paton, William, 1933-1937 (Box 40, Folder 1362)
  - Patr - Patt, 1919-1933 (Box 40, Folder 1363)
  - Patterson, William, 1931-1933 (Box 40, Folder 1364)
  - Pax - Pay, 1915-1946 (Box 40, Folder 1365)
  - Pe - Pel, 1914-1982 (Box 40, Folder 1366)
  - Peltz, William, 1933-1940 (Box 40, Folder 1367)
  - Pence, Owen, 1926-1939 (Box 40, Folder 1368)
  - Pendleton, William, 1943 (Box 40, Folder 1369)
  - Penfield, Thorton B., 1935-1936 (Box 40, Folder 1370)
  - Pennepacker, J. S., 1919 (Box 40, Folder 1371)
  - Pep - Per, 1914-1972 (Box 40, Folder 1372)
  - Perry, Frances, 1936 (Box 40, Folder 1373)
  - Perry, Frank - Perry, Lawrence, 1917-1921 (Box 40, Folder 1374)
  - Pers - Pet, 1916-1976 (Box 40, Folder 1375)
  - Pettus, John de Forest, 1943-1946 (Box 41, Folder 1376)
  - Pettus, W. - Petty, 1926-1937 (Box 41, Folder 1377)
  - Pfanner, Eugene, 1928-1938 (Box 41, Folder 1378)
  - Pfe - Pfl, 1917-1962 (Box 41, Folder 1379)
  - Phelps, Dryden Linsley, 1945 (Box 41, Folder 1380)
  - Phelps, William Lyon, 1916-1940 (Box 41, Folder 1381)
  - Phelps, Z. - Phi, 1915-1927 (Box 41, Folder 1382)
  - Phillips, Marion L., 1917-1944 (Box 41, Folder 1383)
  - Phillips, R. - Phr, 1915-1946 (Box 41, Folder 1384)
  - Pia - Pic, 1917-1941 (Box 41, Folder 1385)
  - Pickett, Herbert E., 1917-1941 (Box 41, Folder 1386)
  - Pickett, J. - Pierce, 1917-1946 (Box 41, Folder 1387)
  - Pier, Stanhope, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 1388)
  - Pierce, Elbridge Bancroft, 1940 (Box 41, Folder 1389)
  - Pierrel, Gren O., 1916-1918 (Box 41, Folder 1390)
  - Pierson, Delavan (Missionary Review of the World), 1916-1917 (Box 41, Folder 1391)
  - Pierson, E. - Pierson, K., 1915-1946 (Box 41, Folder 1392)
  - Pilson, Cornelia, 1955 (Box 41, Folder 1393)
  - Pinchot, Gifford, 1916-1943 (Box 41, Folder 1394)
  - Pine - Pinn, 1927-1946 (Box 41, Folder 1395)
  - Pionteki, J.E., 1916-1917 (Box 41, Folder 1396)
  - Pip - Pit, 1917-1961 (Box 41, Folder 1397)
  - Pitt, Gavin A., 1937-1940 (Box 41, Folder 1398)
  - Pitts - Piv, 1917-1940 (Box 41, Folder 1399)
  - Pla - Plat, 1914-1932 (Box 41, Folder 1400)
  - Platt, Robert S., 1926-1928 (Box 41, Folder 1401)
  - Platt, T. - Ple, 1914-1925 (Box 41, Folder 1402)
  - Plumley, A.R., 1932-1944 (Box 41, Folder 1403)
  - Plums - Plut, 1916-1946 (Box 41, Folder 1404)
  - Poi - Pol, 1938-1955 (Box 41, Folder 1405)
  - Pond, B.circa, 1916-1917 (Box 41, Folder 1406)
  - Pond, N. (?) - Pop, 1920-1946 (Box 41, Folder 1407)
  - Porter, David R.
    - 1914-1916 (Box 41, Folder 1408)
    - 1916-1917 (Box 41, Folder 1409)
    - 1918-1925 (Box 41, Folder 1410)
    - 1925-1930 (Box 41, Folder 1411)
    - 1931-1933 (Box 41, Folder 1412)
    - 1934-1943 (Box 42, Folder 1413)
  - Porter, Frank circa, 1916-1939 (Box 42, Folder 1414)
  - Porter, Fred - Pot, 1916-1944 (Box 42, Folder 1415)
  - Potter, F.M., 1936 (Box 42, Folder 1416)
  - Potter, M. - Pow, 1915-1973 (Box 42, Folder 1417)
  - Powell, Warren T., 1932-1935 (Box 42, Folder 1418)
  - Powell, William D., 1938-1940 (Box 42, Folder 1419)
  - Powers - Powley, 1927-1973 (Box 42, Folder 1420)
  - Pra - Pri, 1915-1946 (Box 42, Folder 1421)
  - Price, David, 1939-1940 (Box 42, Folder 1422)
  - Price, Edward, 1939 (Box 42, Folder 1423)
  - Price, Frank W., 1919-1940 (Box 42, Folder 1424)
  - Price, Guernsey, 1917 (Box 42, Folder 1425)
  - Price, Harry B., 1937-1939 (Box 42, Folder 1426)
  - Price, James Harry, 1943-1946 (Box 42, Folder 1427)
  - Prichard, H. Ayde, 1944 (Box 42, Folder 1428)
  - Prick - Pry, 1916-1945 (Box 42, Folder 1429)
  - Pu - Pur, 1926-1937 (Box 42, Folder 1430)
  - Purdy, Ray Foote, 1925-1928 (Box 42, Folder 1431)
  - Purr - Pux, 1914-1946 (Box 42, Folder 1432)
  - Pye, Ernest, 1930 (Box 42, Folder 1433)
  - Quai - Quinn, 1917-1946 (Box 42, Folder 1434)
  - Quarrier, S.S., 1928 (Box 42, Folder 1435)
  - Rabinowitz, Isaac, 1934 (Box 42, Folder 1436)
  - Rad - Rai, 1918-1973 (Box 42, Folder 1437)
  - Ralla Ram, A., 1942-1944 (Box 42, Folder 1438)
  - Ram, 1928-1963 (Box 42, Folder 1439)
  - Ramsay, John, 1931 (Box 42, Folder 1440)
  - Ramsey, Fred W., 1930 (Box 42, Folder 1441)
  - Ran, 1914-1944 (Box 42, Folder 1442)
  - Rand, Stuart, 1916-1946 (Box 42, Folder 1443)
  - Rankin, Robert, 1940-1963 (Box 42, Folder 1444)
  - Rap - Ray, 1915-1971 (Box 42, Folder 1445)
  - Rea - Rec, 1914-1970 (Box 42, Folder 1446)
  - Reckard, E.circa, Jr., 1939-1956 (Box 42, Folder 1447)
  - Redding, Tracy, 1926-1946 (Box 42, Folder 1448)
  - Red - Reev, 1916-1945 (Box 42, Folder 1449)
  - Reed, Professor Edward B., 1915-1945 (Box 42, Folder 1450)
  - Reed, Harry Lathrop, 1919-1946 (Box 42, Folder 1451)
  - Reed, Howard A., 1940-1956 (Box 43, Folder 1452)
  - Reed, Lansing P., 1916-1939 (Box 43, Folder 1453)
  - Reed, Orville, 1916-1919 (Box 43, Folder 1454)
  - Reeve, Charles Mccirca, 1940-1944 (Box 43, Folder 1455)
  - Reeves, John D., 1935-1936 (Box 43, Folder 1456)
  - Reid - Rein, 1926-1946 (Box 43, Folder 1457)
  - Reid, David, 1931-1939 (Box 43, Folder 1458)
  - Reigeluth, Ray J., 1916-1940 (Box 43, Folder 1459)
  - Reisner, Sherwood, 1940-1946 (Box 43, Folder 1460)
  - Ren - Rey, 1914-1930 (Box 43, Folder 1461)
  - Rettie, J.circa, 1930-1945 (Box 43, Folder 1462)
  - Reuman, Otto G., 1918 (Box 43, Folder 1463)
  - Reynolds, Paul, 1939-1944 (Box 43, Folder 1464)
  - Rhe - Rho, 1917-1938 (Box 43, Folder 1465)
  - Rhodes, I.B., 1925-1927 (Box 43, Folder 1466)
  - Ric - Riz, 1914-1962 (Box 43, Folder 1467)
  - Rice: A - L, 1916-1939 (Box 43, Folder 1468)
  - Rice, Cleaveland J., 1915-1945 (Box 43, Folder 1469)
  - Rich, G. Barrett, 1926-1944 (Box 43, Folder 1470)
  - Rich, Hawley P., 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 1471)
  - Richards: E - K, 1926-1940 (Box 43, Folder 1472)
  - Richards, Henry B., 1915-1926 (Box 43, Folder 1473)
  - Richardson: A - T, 1916-1944 (Box 43, Folder 1474)
  - Richardson, Allan, 1916-1939 (Box 43, Folder 1475)
  - Richardson, Norman, 1939-1940 (Box 43, Folder 1476)
  - Richardson, Ralph J. (Dartmouth Christian Association), 1919-1926 (Box 43, Folder 1477)
  - Richter, Paul G., 1920-1921 (Box 43, Folder 1478)
  - Rife, circaW., 1918 (Box 43, Folder 1479)
  - Riggs: E - D, 1914-1933 (Box 43, Folder 1480)
  - Riggs, Ernest W., 1930-1935 (Box 43, Folder 1481)
  - Riggs, T. Lawrason, 1925-1940 (Box 43, Folder 1482)
  - Riker, Lucetta, 1916-1917 (Box 43, Folder 1483)
  - Rinden, Arthur O., 1925-1945 (Box 43, Folder 1484)
  - Rindge, Fred H., Jr., 1915-1928 (Box 43, Folder 1485)
  - Ritchie, Frank, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 1486)
  - Ritter, Richard H. (Hartford Theological Seminary), 1920-1940 (Box 43, Folder 1487)
  - Rives, F. Bayard, 1925-1940 (Box 43, Folder 1488)
  - Rivkin, David S., 1933-1945 (Box 43, Folder 1489)
  - Rob - Roy, 1913-1971 (Box 43, Folder 1490)
  - Robbins: F - R, 1926-1936 (Box 43, Folder 1491)
  - Robbins, Marcus, 1938-1941 (Box 44, Folder 1492)
  - Robbins, Morton S., 1918 (Box 44, Folder 1493)
  - Robbins, Raymond, 1915-1939 (Box 44, Folder 1494)
  - Roberts: A - R, 1916-1945 (Box 44, Folder 1495)
  - Roberts, Rosamond, 1943 (Box 44, Folder 1496)
  - Roberts, William P., 1918-1944 (Box 44, Folder 1497)
  - Robertson: A - W, 1922-1940 (Box 44, Folder 1498)
  - Robinson: C - W, 1916-1946 (Box 44, Folder 1499)
  - Robinson, Dwight N., 1916-1940 (Box 44, Folder 1500)
  - Robinson, H.E., 1925-1936 (Box 44, Folder 1501)
  - Robinson, James H., 1935-1960 (Box 44, Folder 1502)
  - Rogers: B - R, 1919-1942 (Box 44, Folder 1503)
  - Rogers, Joseph, 1938 (Box 44, Folder 1504)
  - Rogers, William A., 1916-1940 (Box 44, Folder 1505)
  - Rolofson, R.H., 1926 (Box 44, Folder 1506)
  - Rose: C - R, 1917-1945 (Box 44, Folder 1507)
  - Ross: F - R, 1914-1944 (Box 44, Folder 1508)
  - Ross, Wallace M., 1915-1948 (Box 44, Folder 1509)
  - Rossman, G. Parker, 1959-1974 (Box 44, Folder 1510)
  - Rouelle, George, 1916-1917 (Box 44, Folder 1511)
  - Rouse, Ruth, 1944-1945 (Box 44, Folder 1512)
  - Rowe, Harry W., 1917 (Box 44, Folder 1513)
  - Rowland, Wilmina, 1921-1945 (Box 44, Folder 1514)
  - Roy, Andrew, 1936-1945 (Box 44, Folder 1515)
  - Rub - Rv, 1915-1972 (Box 44, Folder 1516)
  - Rudin, Harry R., 1918-1945 (Box 44, Folder 1517)
  - Rugh, Arthur, 1927-1939 (Box 44, Folder 1518)
  - Rugh, Dwight, 1928-1961 (Box 44, Folder 1519)
  - Russ, John circa, 1931-1940 (Box 44, Folder 1520)
  - Russell, Charles A., 1931-1939 (Box 44, Folder 1521)
  - Russell, Robert, 1916-1933 (Box 44, Folder 1522)
  - Rutherford, Gertrude, 1933-1940 (Box 44, Folder 1523)
  - Rutledge, A.E., 1918 (Box 44, Folder 1524)
  - Rya - Ryt, 1916-1957 (Box 44, Folder 1525)
  - Rycroft, W. Stanley, 1945-1946 (Box 44, Folder 1526)
  - Sa - Sal, 1914-1970 (Box 44, Folder 1527)
  - St. John, George, 1916-1943 (Box 44, Folder 1528)
  - St. John, J. - San, 1919-1945 (Box 44, Folder 1529)
  - Sanderson, Benjamin B., 1916-1926 (Box 44, Folder 1530)
  - Sanderson, R.L., 1918 (Box 44, Folder 1531)
  - Sandmel, Samuel, 1946 (Box 44, Folder 1532)
  - Sang - Sar, 1926-1970 (Box 44, Folder 1533)
  - Sargent, Willis H., 1926-1939 (Box 44, Folder 1534)
  - Sargent, Z. - Sar, 1916-1945 (Box 44, Folder 1535)
  - Savage, Donald, 1927-1928 (Box 44, Folder 1536)
  - Savage, Theodore, 1939 (Box 44, Folder 1537)
  - Savage, William R., 1936-1939 (Box 44, Folder 1538)
  - Saw, 1919-1927 (Box 44, Folder 1539)
  - Saxton, E.L., 1925-1938 (Box 44, Folder 1540)
  - Saxton, R. - Say, 1927-1938 (Box 45, Folder 1541)
  - Sayer, Robert H., 1916 (Box 45, Folder 1542)
  - Sayre, John Nevin, 1926-1945 (Box 45, Folder 1543)
  - Sca, 1917-1946 (Box 45, Folder 1544)
  - Scha, 1933-1945 (Box 45, Folder 1545)
  - Schairer, Reinhold, 1925 (Box 45, Folder 1546)
  - Schal - Sche, 1920-1973 (Box 45, Folder 1547)
  - Scherer, Jim, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 1548)
  - Schieffelin, Bayard, 1926 (Box 45, Folder 1549)
  - Schieffelin, Elliot, 1925-1944 (Box 45, Folder 1550)
  - Schieffelin, John J., 1919-1961 (Box 45, Folder 1551)
  - Schieffelin, William, 1915-1926 (Box 45, Folder 1552)
  - Schiel - Schir, 1918-1938 (Box 45, Folder 1553)
  - Schlatter, William J., 1943-1944 (Box 45, Folder 1554)
  - Schle - Schn, 1928-1945 (Box 45, Folder 1555)
  - Schneider, Genevieve, 1925-1945 (Box 45, Folder 1556)
  - Schny - Schr, 1917-1962 (Box 45, Folder 1557)
  - Schroder, Chris: Correspondence, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 1558)
  - Schroeder, John circa, 1939-1946 (Box 45, Folder 1559)
  - Schrum - Schv, 1918-1973 (Box 45, Folder 1560)
  - Schultz, E. B. [Ted], 1930 (Box 45, Folder 1561)
  - Schum - Schw, 1915-1963 (Box 45, Folder 1562)
  - Schwieso, Charles, 1927-1938 (Box 45, Folder 1563)
  - Sco - Scot, 1916-1944 (Box 45, Folder 1564)
  - Scott, Amy, 1934-1935 (Box 45, Folder 1565)
  - Scott, An. - Scott, circa, 1915-1939 (Box 45, Folder 1566)
  - Scott, David A., 1938-1939 (Box 45, Folder 1567)
  - Scott, F. - Scott, H., 1917-1943 (Box 45, Folder 1568)
  - Scott, John W. L. (Loveridge), 1938-1939 (Box 45, Folder 1569)
  - Scott, Ju - Scott, P., 1939-1973 (Box 45, Folder 1570)
  - Scott, Ralph Cleland, 1937-1939 (Box 45, Folder 1571)
  - Scotten - Scov, 1915-1943 (Box 45, Folder 1572)
  - Scoville, William H., 1925-1927 (Box 45, Folder 1573)
  - Scranton, Charles A., 1939-1943 (Box 45, Folder 1574)
  - Scribner, Frank J., 1916-1926 (Box 45, Folder 1575)
  - Scudder, Delton, 1937-1939 (Box 45, Folder 1576)
  - Se - Seac, 1915-1946 (Box 45, Folder 1577)
  - Seaman, Gale, 1917-1939 (Box 45, Folder 1578)
  - Seamans, Harry W., 1935-1945 (Box 45, Folder 1579)
  - Seamans, Herbert L., 1926-1946 (Box 45, Folder 1580)
  - Sear - Seav, 1916-1940 (Box 45, Folder 1581)
  - Sedam, Oscar W., 1930-1931 (Box 45, Folder 1582)
  - See - Sel, 1917-1956 (Box 45, Folder 1583)
  - Selvi, Arturo M., 1946 (Box 45, Folder 1584)
  - Sem - Sey, 1915-1945 (Box 45, Folder 1585)
  - Seymour, Celia B., 1938 (Box 46, Folder 1586)
  - Seymour, Charles, 1918-1949 (Box 46, Folder 1587)
  - Seymour, Morris W., 1916 (Box 46, Folder 1588)
  - Sha, 1913-1946 (Box 46, Folder 1589)
  - Shanley, James, 1939-1941 (Box 46, Folder 1590)
  - Shao - Shap, 1933-1944 (Box 46, Folder 1591)
  - Sharp, David A., 1939-1940 (Box 46, Folder 1592)
  - Sharp, P. - Sharp, R., 1934 (Box 46, Folder 1593)
  - Sharp, Thomas S., 1915-1939 (Box 46, Folder 1594)
  - Sharpe, A. H. (Yale Athletic Association), 1919-1920 (Box 46, Folder 1595)
  - Shat - Shatt, 1915-1939 (Box 46, Folder 1596)
  - Shatluck, S. F., 1938-1971 (Box 46, Folder 1597)
  - Shaw, G., 1928 (Box 46, Folder 1598)
  - Shaw, Mark R., 1916-1941 (Box 46, Folder 1599)
  - Shaw, Ralph M., 1918 (Box 46, Folder 1600)
  - She - Shec, 1915-1934 (Box 46, Folder 1601)
  - Shedd, Clarence P.
    - 1914-1920 (Box 46, Folder 1602)
    - 1920-1931 (Box 46, Folder 1603)
    - 1933-1943 (Box 46, Folder 1604)
    - 1944-1946 (Box 46, Folder 1605)
  - Shee - Shel, 1915-1945 (Box 46, Folder 1606)
  - Shelton, Donald O., 1916-1933 (Box 46, Folder 1607)
  - Shelton, H. - Shep, 1914-1980 (Box 46, Folder 1608)
  - Shepard, Clarence M., 1927-1932 (Box 46, Folder 1609)
  - Shepard, D., 1916-1944 (Box 46, Folder 1610)
  - Shepard, E. - Shepard, J., 1913-1928 (Box 46, Folder 1611)
  - Shepard, Lorrin A., 1916-1936 (Box 46, Folder 1612)
  - Shepard, T. - Sher, 1918-1944 (Box 46, Folder 1613)
  - Sherk, F. A., 1934-1935 (Box 46, Folder 1614)
  - Sherman, A. - Sherman, D., 1914-1974 (Box 46, Folder 1615)
  - Sherman, Nathaniel, 1931-1933 (Box 46, Folder 1616)
  - Sherrill, Henry K., 1915-1945 (Box 47, Folder 1617)
  - Sherrill, Ned, 1943 (Box 47, Folder 1618)
  - Sherry, Esther, 1938 (Box 47, Folder 1619)
  - Sherw - Shev, 1918-1937 (Box 47, Folder 1620)
  - Shi - Ship, 1916-1945 (Box 47, Folder 1621)
  - Shipley, Charles A., 1944-1945 (Box 47, Folder 1622)
  - Shipley, M. - Sho, 1916-1943 (Box 47, Folder 1623)
  - Shoemaker, Robert circa, 1926 (Box 47, Folder 1624)
  - Shoemaker, Samuel M., 1915-1928 (Box 47, Folder 1625)
  - Short, William H., 1919 (Box 47, Folder 1626)
  - Shotts, Claude circa, 1927-1961 (Box 47, Folder 1627)
  - Shotwell, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 1628)
  - Shriver, R. Sargent, 1937-1940 (Box 47, Folder 1629)
  - Shro - Shu, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 1630)
  - Shultz. Edward B., 1919-1933 (Box 47, Folder 1631)
  - Shumaker, K. A., 1937-1946 (Box 47, Folder 1632)
  - Shurter, E. D., 1931 (Box 47, Folder 1633)
  - Si - Sin, 1918-1963 (Box 47, Folder 1634)
  - Simonds, Robert S., 1933-1940 (Box 47, Folder 1635)
  - Simpson, A. - Simpson, H., 1928-1945 (Box 47, Folder 1636)
  - Simpson, Willard - Sinc, 1928-1943 (Box 47, Folder 1637)
  - Simpson, William Gayley, 1918-1926 (Box 47, Folder 1638)
  - Singer, Edgar, 1935 (Box 47, Folder 1639)
  - Sinnott, Edmund W., 1945 (Box 47, Folder 1640)
  - Sir - Siz, 1917-1974 (Box 47, Folder 1641)
  - Sizer, Theodore, 1938-1939 (Box 47, Folder 1642)
  - Sk - Ski, 1915-1955 (Box 47, Folder 1643)
  - Skinner, A. Karl (Rev.), 1921 (Box 47, Folder 1644)
  - Skip - Skl, 1919-1927 (Box 47, Folder 1645)
  - Sla - Slat, 1937-1940 (Box 47, Folder 1646)
  - Sladen, Frank J., 1939-1940 (Box 47, Folder 1647)
  - Slat - Slo, 1916-1961 (Box 47, Folder 1648)
  - Sloane, William, 1913-1944 (Box 47, Folder 1649)
  - Sm - Smal, 1916-1933 (Box 47, Folder 1650)
  - Smart, Daniel S., 1916-1917 (Box 47, Folder 1651)
  - Sme, 1921 (Box 47, Folder 1652)
  - Smith, A. - Smith, circa, 1919-1974 (Box 47, Folder 1653)
  - Smith, David Stanley, 1925-1940, undated (Box 47, Folder 1654)
  - Smith, De. - Smith, H., 1915-1975 (Box 47, Folder 1655)
  - Smith, Harry Hedley, 1917-1939 (Box 47, Folder 1656)
  - Smith, He. - Smith, R., 1917-1946 (Box 47, Folder 1657)
  - Smith, Robert Ashton, 1938-1943 (Box 47, Folder 1658)
  - Smith, Robert Seneca, 1936-1938 (Box 47, Folder 1659)
  - Smith, Ro. - Smith, W., 1914-1939 (Box 47, Folder 1660)
  - Smith, Wilbert B., 1913-1943 (Box 47, Folder 1661)
  - Smith, William, 1933 (Box 47, Folder 1662)
  - Smith, William Kyle, 1939-1940 (Box 47, Folder 1663)
  - Smith, Winthrop A., undated (Box 47, Folder 1664)
  - Smu - Smy, 1939-1940 (Box 47, Folder 1665)
  - Smyth, Winifred, 1916-1925 (Box 47, Folder 1666)
  - Sn - Sp, 1916-1961 (Box 47, Folder 1667)
  - Speare, Margaret, 1925 (Box 47, Folder 1668)
  - Speer, Emma Bailey, 1937-1938 (Box 47, Folder 1669)
  - Speer, Elliott E., 1916-1933 (Box 47, Folder 1670)
  - Speer, Margaret Bailey, 1937 (Box 47, Folder 1671)
  - Speer, Robert E., 1913-1939 (Box 48, Folder 1672)
  - Speers, James M., 1936 (Box 48, Folder 1673)
  - Speers, T. - Spi, 1916-1964 (Box 48, Folder 1674)
  - Spivack, Robert G., 1939-1941 (Box 48, Folder 1675)
  - Spo - Sr, 1916-1961 (Box 48, Folder 1676)
  - Stabler, W. Brooke, 1931-1945 (Box 48, Folder 1677)
  - Stabner - Stac, 1944-1981 (Box 48, Folder 1678)
  - Stackpole, Markham W., 1916-1925 (Box 48, Folder 1679)
  - Stae - Stan, 1919-1961 (Box 48, Folder 1680)
  - Stanley, Francis A., 1925-1940 (Box 48, Folder 1681)
  - Stanley, H. G., 1920-1944 (Box 48, Folder 1682)
  - Stanley, J., 1916-1962 (Box 48, Folder 1683)
  - Stauffer, Milton, 1925-1934 (Box 48, Folder 1684)
  - Stearns, Alfred E., 1916-1926 (Box 48, Folder 1685)
  - Stebbins, Edwin Allen, 1915-1938 (Box 48, Folder 1686)
  - Stebbins, H. Lyman, 1932-1933 (Box 48, Folder 1687)
  - Stebbins, Henry H., 1939-1940 (Box 48, Folder 1688)
  - Stee - Steen, 1926-1934 (Box 48, Folder 1689)
  - Steere, Douglas, 1933-1940 (Box 48, Folder 1690)
  - Steese - Stei, 1913-1946 (Box 48, Folder 1691)
  - Steinert, Rudolph, 1916-1926 (Box 48, Folder 1692)
  - Steinh - Step, 1919-1969 (Box 48, Folder 1693)
  - Sterling, Edward circa, 1945 (Box 48, Folder 1694)
  - Ster - Stes, 1930-1933 (Box 48, Folder 1695)
  - Stevanovich, Emilio, 1946 (Box 48, Folder 1696)
  - Stevens - Stevenson, 1914-1962 (Box 48, Folder 1697)
  - Stevenson, Donald D., 1926-1941 (Box 48, Folder 1698)
  - Stevenson, J. - Stew, 1916-1945 (Box 48, Folder 1699)
  - Stewart, George
    - 1915-1917 (Box 48, Folder 1700)
    - 1918-1919 (Box 48, Folder 1701)
    - 1919 (Box 48, Folder 1702)
    - 1919 (Box 48, Folder 1703)
    - 1919-1920 (Box 49, Folder 1704)
    - 1920 (Box 49, Folder 1705)
    - 1920-1921 (Box 49, Folder 1706)
    - 1921 (Box 49, Folder 1707)
    - 1921 (Box 49, Folder 1708)
    - 1921-1930 (Box 49, Folder 1709)
    - 1930-1934 (Box 49, Folder 1710)
    - 1934-1936 (Box 49, Folder 1711)
    - 1936-1938 (Box 49, Folder 1712)
    - 1938-1939 (Box 49, Folder 1713)
    - 1939-1944 (Box 50, Folder 1714)
    - 1944-1971 (Box 50, Folder 1715)
    - no date (Box 50, Folder 1716)
  - Stewart, M. - Sto, 1915-1956 (Box 50, Folder 1717)
  - Stoddard, circa F., 1944-1962 (Box 50, Folder 1718)
  - Stod - Stok, 1916-1933 (Box 50, Folder 1719)
  - Stokes, Anson Phelps, 1913-1946 (Box 50, Folder 1720)
  - Stokes, Harold P., 1916-1926 (Box 50, Folder 1721)
  - Stokes, I. - Ston, 1925-1934 (Box 50, Folder 1722)
  - Stone, John Timothy, 1916-1918 (Box 50, Folder 1723)
  - Stone, Louis, 1938 (Box 50, Folder 1724)
  - Stone, Wilfred S., 1940 (Box 50, Folder 1725)
  - Stones - Str, 1919-1971 (Box 50, Folder 1726)
  - Stringham, James, 1927-1938 (Box 50, Folder 1727)
  - Stromberg, Ashbury G., 1939 (Box 50, Folder 1728)
  - Strong, Esther, 1937-1939 (Box 50, Folder 1729)
  - Strong, H. - Strong, R., 1916-1940 (Box 50, Folder 1730)
  - Strong, Theodore, 1916-1917 (Box 50, Folder 1731)
  - Strong, Tracy, 1935-1958 (Box 50, Folder 1732)
  - Strov - Stry, 1928-1943 (Box 50, Folder 1733)
  - Stu - Stud, 1915-1919 (Box 50, Folder 1734)
  - Studley, Jeanette, 1933-1934 (Box 50, Folder 1735)
  - Studw - Stux, 1916-1944 (Box 50, Folder 1736)
  - Su - Sut, 1913-1962 (Box 50, Folder 1737)
  - Suttie, Roscoe H., 1940-1945 (Box 50, Folder 1738)
  - Sw - Swan, 1919-1946 (Box 50, Folder 1739)
  - Swan, Eugene LaForest, 1916-1940 (Box 50, Folder 1740)
  - Swan, H. - Sway, 1919-1970 (Box 50, Folder 1741)
  - Sw - Swe, 1919-1945 (Box 50, Folder 1742)
  - Sweetman, Ray, 1916-1946 (Box 50, Folder 1743)
  - Sweetman, W., 1937-1939 (Box 50, Folder 1744)
  - Swenson, Edward F., 1939-1956 (Box 50, Folder 1745)
  - Swenston - Swet, 1916-1926 (Box 50, Folder 1746)
  - Swift, A. Ervine, 1943-1945 (Box 50, Folder 1747)
  - Swift, Charles, 1918-1945 (Box 51, Folder 1748)
  - Swift, Charles, undated (Box 51, Folder 1749)
  - Swift, David, 1933-1940 (Box 51, Folder 1750)
  - Swift, W., 1916-1926 (Box 51, Folder 1751)
  - Swo - Sy, 1915-1972 (Box 51, Folder 1752)
  - Ta, 1918-1962 (Box 51, Folder 1753)
  - Taft, Charles P., 1919-1943 (Box 51, Folder 1754)
  - Taft, Horace D., 1920-1973 (Box 51, Folder 1755)
  - Taft, William H., 1913-1919 (Box 51, Folder 1756)
  - Tate, Mowbray, 1944 (Box 51, Folder 1757)
  - Taylor, Effie J., 1939-1940 (Box 51, Folder 1758)
  - Taylor, E. Hall, 1925-1944 (Box 51, Folder 1759)
  - Taylor, Harry B., 1933 (Box 51, Folder 1760)
  - Taylor, Susan (Vassar College), 1927 (Box 51, Folder 1761)
  - Te, 1919-1944 (Box 51, Folder 1762)
  - Terlin, Rose, 1937-1939 (Box 51, Folder 1763)
  - Terry, H.P. Baldwin, 1955 (Box 51, Folder 1764)
  - Terry, Seth Sprague, 1925-1928 (Box 51, Folder 1765)
  - Th, 1914-1981 (Box 51, Folder 1766)
  - Thacher, Sherman D., 1916-1926 (Box 51, Folder 1767)
  - Theuer, George, 1935-1944 (Box 51, Folder 1768)
  - Thienes, Elmer T., 1920-1921 (Box 51, Folder 1769)
  - Thierman, Ian, 1939-1943 (Box 51, Folder 1770)
  - Thomas, John M., 1925-1943 (Box 51, Folder 1771)
  - Thomas, Norman, 1917-1944 (Box 51, Folder 1772)
  - Thompson, Hugo, 1926-1939 (Box 51, Folder 1773)
  - Thomsen, Eric, 1925-1933 (Box 51, Folder 1774)
  - Thomson, Henrietta, 1932-1934 (Box 51, Folder 1775)
  - Thorne, Samuel B., 1926-1943 (Box 51, Folder 1776)
  - Thorne, Victor circa, 1938-1940 (Box 51, Folder 1777)
  - Thrall, Barbara, 1939 (Box 51, Folder 1778)
  - Thurber, L. Newton, 1944 (Box 51, Folder 1779)
  - Ti, 1914-1938 (Box 51, Folder 1780)
  - Tibbets, Walter I., 1916-1926 (Box 51, Folder 1781)
  - Tinker, Chauncey B., 1915-1931 (Box 51, Folder 1782)
  - Tinker, Wellington H., 1915-1939 (Box 51, Folder 1783)
  - Tittle, Ernest F., 1926-1939 (Box 51, Folder 1784)
  - To, 1915-1961 (Box 52, Folder 1785)
  - Tobias, Channing H., 1938-1944 (Box 52, Folder 1786)
  - Toumey, H.D., 1917-1918 (Box 52, Folder 1787)
  - Towle, Gifford, 1931-1935 (Box 52, Folder 1788)
  - Towner, W. Sibley, 1955-1956 (Box 52, Folder 1789)
  - Townsend, Constance L., 1927-1940 (Box 52, Folder 1790)
  - Tr - Ts, 1915-1944 (Box 52, Folder 1791)
  - Trowbridge, Buel, 1928-1933 (Box 52, Folder 1792)
  - Truesdale, Melville D., 1920 (Box 52, Folder 1793)
  - Truesdell, Reita, 1937 (Box 52, Folder 1794)
  - Trull, George H., 1932-1933 (Box 52, Folder 1795)
  - Tryon, Harold H., 1939-1940 (Box 52, Folder 1796)